Lieutenant Colonel.
Yes. I just saw them.
They've come to block our path.
Can we dodge them?
Not easily.
I told you.
Turning's not this baby's thing.
I'll handle them.
Don't worry. Just head for the Morpho.
How?
I was hoping I could land
before you got off, but...
Are you going to drop us?
From this altitude?
Don't worry! We built it really fast,
but it should still work!
Don't worry about us.
I brought a spare.
Lt. Colonel, if you're just distracting the enemy,
you don't need to fight.
After making contact,
evacuate to the forest.
Oh, thank you.
But... don't underestimate me, kid.
May the speed of the gods protect us!
The Nachzehrer...
Prepare for impact, everyone.
Lieutenant Colonel...
Let's go.
We've lost contact with the Nachzehrer!
All troops were dropped before the signal was lost,
and they are still active.
But we've just received word from Lt. Nouzen
that they've encountered the enemy.
The enemy has built a defensive perimeter.
What's Nordlicht's situation?
The task force is currently in combat
with the Morpho's defenders
and is approaching the target.
Hey, are they leading us somewhere?
Well, Commander?
With this many around us,
Shin's ears alone can't help.
We'll just have to keep going!
Here come some more!
Shin!
That's it?
It's that big?
The Morpho's kind of like a millipede.
More like a centipede?
It's got long legs,
and it's kind of squirming around.
It doesn't matter.
It's disgusting either way.
Læraðr HQ, we've sighted the enemy near the
high-speed train terminal at Kreutzbek City.
It doesn't seem
to have finished its repairs.
This is Læraðr HQ, roger.
A United Kingdom observation unit is nearby.
Roger. We will now begin combat.
It moved!
I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
It's fixed?
What do we do?
Commander!
I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
I'll...
Get back, Shinei!
What you're seeing isn't Kiri!
I'll kill you!
I'll kill you all!
Everyone, retreat! Now!
What's wrong?
I'll explain later!
Roger!
Impact confirmed
near Kreutzbek City terminal!
Likely a Morpho attack!
Impossible!
It wasn't supposed to repair itself!
If it wasn't a repair, but a swap-out...
It would've been faster
to put an undamaged core into a spare.
So they've succeeded in luring us out...
All United Kingdom observers
were lost in the attack.
Those goddamn pieces of scrap!
We've got no choice
but to do a saturation missile strike.
It's useless.
Where would you fire these missiles?
We don't know the enemy's location.
Our radar's down.
We have no observation drones!
It's a rail-based cannon!
If we can destroy the tracks...
It can hit most of our forward bases
from where it is, right?
And they'd repair the rails in no time.
We'd be wasting missiles.
With Nordlicht's failure,
we have no other choice.
We need to protect the western front
from artillery attack,
even if it's just for now.
And what will you after "now" passes?
Send in another team?
Without even a way to open
a path home for them?
Abandoning the soldiers you sent
into enemy territory to protect yourself,
giving up on the rest of the plan...
That's disgusting behavior.
Beneath humanity.
As the Federacy's provisional President
and its Commander-in-Chief,
do you think I'd allow that?
The Federacy has higher ideals to uphold.
If we're talking about giving up on that,
we'd be better off destroyed.
You allowed me become President,
and now you must live with the consequences!
If you insist that the only way
we can survive is an unethical one,
then you'll have to die here
along with my ideals.
It seems that may be unnecessary.
All members of Nordlicht have survived!
They're still attempting to destroy the Morpho!
To think the real one was somewhere else...
Even you couldn't tell?
We're changing targets, everyone.
Heading 2-8-0. Distance 5000.
Equip HEAT rounds.
Get into position.
Roger!
Fire!
Damn it!
Pale Rider to No-Face.
Prescribed firing schedule complete.
Special target with the call sign "Baleygr"
was successfully lured in and destroyed.
The analysis was correct.
Baleygr could not detect the spare
when it was in sleep mode.
No-Face to Pale Rider.
Confirm Baleygr's destruction.
Pale Rider to No-Face. Unnecessary.
Baleygr was certainly destroyed.
No-Face, roger.
Leave your firing position,
and return to your designated district.
Roger.
Survivors?
Maggots.
Do you think your little guns can defeat me?
Baleygr!
It can still move?
Impossible...
That's...
You're still alive?
I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
Still too far...
Now what? Fire again, Shin?
Shin!
No-Face to Pale Rider.
You are instructed to leave the enemy
to your escorts and withdraw.
Pale Rider to No-Face.
That order is unacceptable.
I'll destroy the enemy.
No-Face to Pale Rider.
I repeat.
You are instructed to leave the enemy
to your escorts
and withdraw from the combat zone.
I'll kill you!
Shin!
If you make your desire to kill me
that obvious, it's easy.
I'll kill you!
What's wrong? Shin!
The enemy Feldreß has the advantage
at this range.
In addition, your weapons are likely
to be fatal to Baleygr.
Shin! What's wrong?
Shin!
I'll kill you!
For these reasons, you are not permitted
to participate in this battle.
You are ordered to return to your
designated district and fight there.
I repeat. You are to withdraw
from this combat area.
Roger.
I won't let him get away!
Shin!
What's wrong? Can't you hear me!
Shin, can't you hear me?
Shin!
The Legion are back!
They're going to surround us!
What do we do, Shin?!
Shin! Shin! Shin!
Follow the Morpho?
Are you insane?
If we're all together,
we can last until the main force gets here!
Our objective is to destroy the Morpho,
not take this town.
Let's go.
Why are you Eighty-Six so willing to risk your lives
for a country that isn't even yours?
Sheesh...
My luck ran out
when I got you as my boss!
This is gonna get me killed.
Listen up, everybody!
Turn around!
You're in luck. You love hell,
and you're gonna get it!
We'll handle this area.
I hate to say it, but even
we can't keep up with your mobility.
I don't want to be the one
to slow you down.
Good luck.
Thanks.
That mark...
It belongs to the Nouzen clan.
Follow me, Baleygr.
You're like me.
You have no place,
except on the battlefield...
But if you still intend to cling
to your pathetic life...
I'll teach you...
I'll destroy your comrades you command,
the land you call home...
I'll burn them right in front of you!
I'll make it so you're all alone.
Time Since Mission Began
I want to confirm this again.
Your small force moves much faster
than an entire army.
We can't offer artillery support,
let alone air support.
Or send reinforcements.
Will you still continue your pursuit?
Fire support and reinforcements
from the main force
were never part the plan.
There's no other way.
It's embarrassing
to hear you say that, though.
Just because we left it to you once
doesn't mean it has to stay that way
once the situation has changed. It's not fair.
If you've changed your mind,
you can fall back.
You're joking.
Every minute we spend retreating is a minute
the Morpho gets deeper into Legion-held territory
and becomes harder to destroy.
If you withdraw and are sent home,
it won't matter how difficult
the mission is to accomplish.
If we can't defeat the Morpho,
we'll die anyway.
Retreating today only to die tomorrow
is meaningless.
I see.
Very well.
That's all from me.
Any questions?
No.
Temporary Command Post
Eastern Kreutzbek City
They weren't even slightly interested.
I guess their attention is elsewhere.
I hate to say it, but they're going to die
in battle sooner or later.
They weren't even worried about you,
I'm sad to say.
Of course not.
If I had kids ten years younger
worrying about me,
I'd die of shame.
I'm sure you managed to avoid combat,
but I'm still impressed
you made it home alive.
I see your skills are as sharp as ever,
Spider-Woman.
The Black Widow who slays the Legion.
Stop that, Murderous Praying Mantis.
You know where that name came from, right?
Of course.
I'm the one who came up with it.
There aren't many brides
who had to wear mourning clothes
for their husband's funeral
before they got to wear a wedding dress.
You're terrible.
The Major General and I were ready to annoy you
by filling the wedding hall with roses.
This is what you get for rejecting me,
and going with an idiot
who left his wife behind.
I don't care about the monsters.
But I don't want to see you
crying over them again.
Meow! Meow! Meow!
A cat?
Are you stupid?
She's in heat.
Open it, Fido.
That's an order.
Open it!
No, Fido!
Don't open it up!
What are you doing?!
Why did you follow us?!
If something happens,
you'll die with us!
Because I don't like
the way you think, fools!
How long are you going to keep thinking
you're in District 86,
where you have to die?
Even Ernst told you to come back!
That is your task right now.
I'm a hostage.
Not to keep you from running
from the battlefield,
but to keep you from running
from your duty to come home alive!
Even you wouldn't want a frail little girl
like me to die with you, right?
Raiden, if I told you to take her back...
Don't be ridiculous.
The only person who could do that
would be you.
Really.
I can't get past all the Legion
between us and the main force.
Want to go with Fido, then?
I can't see that working.
Fine. I'll take her.
She won't fit
in anybody else's but mine, right?
Thank you.
Never do this again.
You didn't have to do this.
We're not going to die.
Okay...
I'm sorry.
Okay, let's eat lunch.
Yeah, we were getting it ready just now.
We'll need to make another.
Frederica.
You know how to use it, right?
If we get wiped out, and you can't
meet up with the main army...
Use it on yourself.
Are you sure?
This is the gun you used
on Eugene... your comrades.
I told you to close your eyes.
Fool. I saw your memories.
You carry them all.
It's too heavy for a frail little girl like me.
I'm giving it right back to you
when we get back to base.
So make sure you come with me.
"Together unto death."